

# TAN PO HUI

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEEER

## **SUMMARY**

I'm a front-end developer with experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, React.js, Next,js. I've applied these skills in diverse projects, including *Game Hub* using React with TypeScript and Bootstrap, and *Issue Tracker* with Next.js and Tailwind CSS. Alongside my technical abilities, I've cultivated soft skills like leadership and teamwork through part-time roles. In a nutshell, I believe that my blend of hard and soft skills can enhance productivity and add value to any team.

# CONTACT



011-2161-9787



phxx04@gmail.com



76, Jalan Jaya Mas 4, Skudai, Johor

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Asia Pasific University**

Diploma in Informatic & Communication Technology with specialism in Software Engineering

2022 - 2024

## LANGUAGES

- Chinese
- Malay
- English

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **Acting Leader**

Tsutaya Bookstore | 2022 - 2024

- As team leader when necessary.
- Guilding temas within 10 members.
- Make decisions in the absence of the regular leader, ensuring that operations continue smoothly.
- Assigning tasks, prioritizing work, taking corrective actions, and updating records.

## EVENT PARTICIPATED

#### Web3 101: More than Crytocurrency

Asia Pasific University

27 JAN 2024 - 28 JAN 2024

#### **AWS Student Symposium**

Asia Pasific University

21 MARCH 2024

## **SKILLS**

#### HARD SKILLS

- Front-End Developer
- HTML, CSS, JS, TS, PYTHON, PHP, SQL, JAVA
- Framework React, Next

#### SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership
- Strong organizational and timemanagement skills
- Ability to work independently and as part of a team